texto=<font face="Arial" size="14"> 
 Dygoil Cia Ltda, a hundred percent Ecuadorian company established in Ecuador in March 1986 with the aim of providing oilfield services, consulting and representation in the various areas of national and international hydrocarbon industry. 
 Began its activities with the vision of two young Petroleum Engineers with vast experience in this sector, <b>Mauro Dávalos Cordero and Cesar Guerra Navarrete</b>, whose surname, Dávalos and Guerra born DYGOIL’s name. - They faced the challenge of providing specialized services in areas as complex as the oil services, which previously were exclusively managed by foreign companies, making Dygoil <b>"Pioneer in the National Oil Services”</b>. 
 <b>Our motto: "The Excellence in Service"</b> is a fundamental part of the culture of our human capital, endeavoring at all times to continuous improvement, working in strict harmony with the environment, and all times we are concerned about the health and safety of our workers. 
</font>
