texto=<font face="Arial" size="14"> 
We have made every effort to maintain our daily motto "The Excellence in Service" which has been recognized by domestic and foreign customers. 
Dygoil continues playing the leadership in the Ecuadorian hydrocarbon sector, maintaining its well deserved title "Pioneers in the National Oil Services" 
Our greatest satisfaction: continue to generate employment for more than a thousand families in different areas of work in our specialty. 
Therefore, we continue with the same optimism and hope in our Country's oil future. 
Ing. César Guerra
                                                                                                                                     
</font>